#### Contact

hainpx89@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ nguyenphamxuanhai (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

User Experience Design (UED)
Wireframing
Software Development

Languages

English

# Nguyen Pham Xuan Hai

**UX/UI** Designer

Vietnam

## Summary

Experienced User Experience Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the outsourcing/offshoring industry. Skilled in Game Design, Logo Design, Painting, and Strategic Planning from VTC Intercom. Skilled in Software Design and Strategic Planning from FPT software, Viettel Corporation . Strong skill design professional graduated from Arena Multimedia.

# Experience

Viettel Group
UX/UI Designer
August 2022 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Freelance

User Experience Designer March 2014 - Present (11 years 1 month)

Hanoi

Digital Division SHB Bank
UX/UI Designer
December 2021 - July 2022 (8 months)
Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Viettel Group

Product Design Engineer

April 2019 - December 2021 (2 years 9 months)

- Create high-fidelity interface design comps (mockups) for use across multiple platforms and form factors, including large-screen interactive displays, PCs, tablets and phones
- Produce sketches and wireframes in support of collaborative brainstorming sessions
- Regularly present and discuss work and ideas with product collaborators
- Accept constructive feedback and creative direction

- Make sure all design work adheres to a unified brand design language and style guide
- Stay up to date with modern trends in design and technology.

#### **FPT Software**

#### **UX/UI** Designer

September 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 7 months)

- Create, update designs based on requirements
- Create mockup and prototype for presentation and overview the workflow
- Fixing bug or issue related to user interface and graphic designs
- Post questions to get more information from BA,PO and development team
- Report defects, and verify defects when they are fixed
- Support other members when they need
- Software: Photoshop, Illustrator, Basamiq Mockup, Sketch, Adobe XD.

#### VTC Online

#### Junior UI Designer

April 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 6 months)

- Design POSM for the seminars, career events, MKT campaign... such as backdrop, banner, standee...
- Desgin logo, key visual and other materials for MKT campaign.
- Design Recruitment Advertising Package: landing page, banner...
- UI/UX Game Design, Website, App.
- Software: Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, Spine.

### INTERSPACE VIỆT NAM - ACCESSTRADE

#### **Graphic Designer**

January 2015 - April 2016 (1 year 4 months)

Product: ACCESSTRADE, one of the largest CPA affiliate platform in Japan & Southeast Asia, since 1999. ACCESSTRADE is the Pioneer and Leading affiliate platform in Vietnam since 2015 and has expanding to Indonesia, Thailand, Singapore, and Malaysia.

Company size: 50-200 employees; https://accesstrade.vn/

- Design POSM for the seminars, career events, MKT campaign... such as backdrop, banner, standee...
- Desgin logo, key visual and other materials for MKT campaign.
- Design Recruitment Advertising Package: landing page, banner...
- Design layout on ACCESSTRADE and INTERSPACE website.

VCCorp Corporation Graphic Designer January 2013 - January 2015 (2 years 1 month) Vietnam

Design Banner, Poster, Retouch Images, Motion Graphic for Game Project.

Vietnam Television Video Editor February 2012 - January 2013 (1 year)

# Education

Arena Multimedia Advance Diploma in Multimedia

Hanoi University of Science and Technology
College's degree, Computer/Information Technology Administration and
Management